<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vault</title><link>https://lucasbarronio.github.io/obsidian-repo/</link><description>Recent content on Vault</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>pt-br</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lucasbarronio.github.io/obsidian-repo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Linguagem C</title><link>https://lucasbarronio.github.io/obsidian-repo/100_Programming/C/C/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasbarronio.github.io/obsidian-repo/100_Programming/C/C/</guid><description>What is C? C is a general-purpose programming language created by Dennis Ritchie at the Bell Laboratories in 1972.
It is a very popular language, despite being old. The main reason for its popularity is because it is a fundamental language in the field of computer science.
C is strongly associated with UNIX, as it was developed to write the UNIX operating system.
Why Learn C? It is one of the most popular programming languages in the world If you know C, you will have no problem learning other popular programming languages such as Java, Python, C++, C#, etc, as the syntax is similar If you know C, you will understand how computer memory works C is very fast, compared to other programming languages, like Java and Python C is very versatile; it can be used in both applications and technologies Difference between C and C++ C++ was developed as an extension of C, and both languages have almost the same syntax The main difference between C and C++ is that C++ supports classes and objects, while C does not.</description></item><item><title>Linguagem PHP</title><link>https://lucasbarronio.github.io/obsidian-repo/100_Programming/PHP/PHP/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lucasbarronio.github.io/obsidian-repo/100_Programming/PHP/PHP/</guid><description>What You Should Already Know Before you continue you should have a basic understanding of the following:
HTML CSS JavaScript If you want to study these subjects first, find the tutorials on our Home page.
What is PHP? PHP is an acronym for &amp;ldquo;PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor&amp;rdquo; PHP is a widely-used, open source scripting language PHP scripts are executed on the server PHP is free to download and use PHP is an amazing and popular language!</description></item></channel></rss>